<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kdegraphics_mobipocket</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <name>kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-grafik mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxkdegraphics-mobipocketxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">kgradichics-mobipocket</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">kdegraphics-mobipocket</name>
  <summary>A plugin to show Mobi e-book files as thumbnails in KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un connector per a mostrar fitxers de llibre electrònic Mobi com a miniatures a les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Modul zur Anzeige von Mobipocket-E-Books als Vorschaubilder in KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ένα πρόσθετο που εμφανίζει τα αρχεία ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων Mobi ως εικόνες επισκόπησης στις εφαρμογές του KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A plugin to show Mobi e-book files as thumbnails in KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un complemento para mostrar archivos de libros electrónicos Mobi como miniaturas en aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDE aplikazioetan Mobi e-liburu fitxategiak koadro-txiki gisa erakusteko plugin bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un module externe permettant d'afficher les livres électroniques Mobi en tant que vignettes dans les applications KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un'estensione per visualizzare nelle applicazioni KDE le miniature dei file degli ebook Mobi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램에서 Mobi 전자책 파일을 미리 보는 플러그인</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een plug-in om Mobi e-bookbestanden als miniaturen in KDE toepassingen te tonen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wtyczka do pokazywania plików e-booków Mobi jako miniatury w aplikacjach KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um 'plugin' para mostrar os ficheiros e-book da Mobi como miniaturas nas aplicações do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um plugin para mostrar os arquivos de e-book Mobi como miniaturas nos aplicativos do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett insticksprogram för att visa Mobi e-böcker som miniatyrbilder i KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Додаток для показу мініатюр вмісту файлів електронних книг Mobi у програмах KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA plugin to show Mobi e-book files as thumbnails in KDE applicationsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">用于在 KDE 应用程序中以缩略图展示 Mobi 电子书文件的一个插件</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">可以在 KDE 應用程式將 Mobi e-book 檔案顯示成縮圖的外掛程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This plugin shows thumbnails of Mobipocket e-books in Dolphin and other KDE apps.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest connector mostra les miniatures dels llibres electrònics Mobipocket al Dolphin i altres aplicacions KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dieses Modul zeigt Vorschaubilder von Mobipocket-E-Books in Dolphin und KDE-Anwendungen</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτό το πρόσθετο εμφανίζει εικόνες επισκόπησης των ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων Mobipocket στο Dolphin και σε άλλες εφαρμογές του KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This plugin shows thumbnails of Mobipocket e-books in Dolphin and other KDE apps.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este complemento muestra miniaturas de libros electrónicos Mobipocket en Dolphin y en otras aplicaciones de KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin honek Mobipocket e-liburuen koadro-txikiak erakusten ditu Dolphinen eta beste KDE aplikazioetan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ce module externe affiche les vignettes des livres électroniques Mobipocket dans Dolphin et d'autres applications KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questa estensione mostra le miniature degli ebook Mobipocket in Dolphin e in altre applicazioni di KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 플러그인은 Dolphin이나 다른 KDE 앱에 Mobipocket 전자책 미리 보기를 표시합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze plug-in toont miniaturen van Mobipocket e-books in Dolphin en andere KDE toepassingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ta wtyczka pokazuje miniatury e-booków Mobipocket w Dolphinie i innych aplikacjach KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Este 'plugin' mostra miniaturas dos e-books da Mobipocket no Dolphin e nas outras aplicações do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Este plugin mostra miniaturas dos e-books Mobipocket no Dolphin e nos outros aplicativos do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Insticksprogrammet visar miniatyrbilder av Mobipocket e-böcker i Dolphin och andra KDE-program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цього додатка можна користуватися мініатюрами вмісту електронних книг Mobipocket у Dolphin та інших програмах KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis plugin shows thumbnails of Mobipocket e-books in Dolphin and other KDE apps.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">此插件在 Dolphin 和其他 KDE 应用程序中展示 Mobipocket 电子书的缩略图。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">這個外掛程式會在 Dolphin 及其他 KDE 應用程式顯示 Mobipocket e-book 的縮圖。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdegraphics-mobipocket/kdegraphics-mobipocket.png</image>
      <caption>Dolphin with Mobi e-book thumbnail</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Dolphin amb miniatures de llibre electrònic Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Dolphin mit der Vorschau einer Mobipocket-E-Book-Datei</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Το Dolphin με εικόνες επισκόπησης των ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Dolphin with Mobi e-book thumbnail</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Dolphin con miniaturas de libros electrónicos Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Dolphin Mobi e-liburuen koadro-txiki egilearekin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Dolphin avec une vignette de livre électronique Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Dolphin con le miniature degli ebook Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Mobi 전자책 미리 보기가 표시된 Dolphin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Dolphin met Mobi e-book-miniatuur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Dolphin z miniaturami e-bookow Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O Dolphin com uma miniatura de e-book da Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">O Dolphin com uma miniatura de e-book Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Dolphin s miniatúrou e-knihy Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Dolphin med miniatyrbild för Mobi e-bok</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Dolphin із мініатюрою електронної книги Mobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDolphin with Mobi e-book thumbnailxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">使 Dolphin 支持 Mobi 电子书缩略图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Dolphin 和 Mobi e-book 縮圖</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">calibre-ebook-edit</icon>
</component>
